Welcome back English learners.
欢迎回来，英语学习者。
My name is Marco and I am joined by...
我是Marco，和我一起的是...
Erika.
Erika。
How are you Erika?
你好吗，Erika？
I'm doing great.
我很好。
Marco and you?
Marco，你呢？
Excellent.
非常好。
I'm doing really well and I'm really excited about our lesson for today.
我状态很好，而且对今天的课程非常期待。
That's right.
没错。
We've got an intermediate lesson today and we're going to study some real English.
今天我们有一节中级课程，我们要学习一些真正的英语。
English that you use every day, right?
你每天都会用到的英语，对吧？
That's right.
没错。
English that native speakers really use.
母语者真正使用的英语。
Exactly.
正是如此。
So today, as Erika mentioned, we have an intermediate lesson and not only is it intermediate, but
所以今天，正如Erika提到的，我们有一节中级课程，而且不仅是中级，还是
it's a business lesson.
一节商务课程。
Yes.
是的。
So today we're listening in to a sales meeting and we're going to learn some great useful
今天我们听一段销售会议，学习一些非常实用的
English to talk about sales strategies.
谈论销售策略的英语。
So we're going to learn English for sales strategies, for making suggestions and for
所以我们要学习关于销售策略、提出建议和
responding to suggestions.
回应建议的英语。
Great.
太好了。
So why don't we take a look at our vocabulary preview for today?
那我们来看看今天的词汇预览吧？
Vocabulary preview.
词汇预览。
So our vocabulary preview is a part of our lesson when we teach you some really important
词汇预览是我们课程的一部分，我们会教你们一些非常重要的
words that will help you to understand the dialogue better.
单词，帮助你们更好地理解对话。
Okay, great.
好的，太好了。
So that is what vocabulary preview is.
这就是词汇预览。
We have two words for you today and we can start off by looking at the first one.
今天我们有两个单词，我们可以先看第一个。
Our first word today is drive sales.
今天的第一个单词是 drive sales。
Drive sales.
Drive sales。
To drive sales.
To drive sales。
And that means?
那是什么意思？
To increase sales.
增加销售额。
Right.
对。
To sell more.
卖得更多。
Exactly.
正是如此。
So to drive sales.
所以是 drive sales。
Okay.
好的。
So now let's look at our second word and it's an interesting one.
现在我们来看第二个词，这个词很有意思。
It's promotion.
这个词是促销。
Promotion.
促销。
So, Erika, what is a promotion exactly?
那么，Erika，促销到底是什么？
Okay.
好的。
So here we're not really talking about getting a better job, right?
这里我们说的不是升职，对吧？
Okay.
好的。
Not like a job promotion.
不是工作晋升那种。
No.
不是。
We're talking about a marketing strategy.
我们说的是营销策略。
Okay.
好的。
So I can give you an example.
我可以给你举个例子。
Suppose that I want to buy shampoo.
假设我想买洗发水。
And if I go to the supermarket and I see buy one and get one free.
如果我去超市，看到买一送一。
So that's a two for one.
那就是买二付一。
That's a two for one promotion.
那是买二付一的促销。
Yeah.
对。
Okay.
好的。
That's a sales promotion.
那是销售促销。
Or?
或者？
Perhaps the shampoo in the supermarket is less expensive than usual.
也许超市里的洗发水比平时便宜。
Maybe, yeah, usually maybe it costs $5 but today it costs $4.
可能，嗯，通常可能卖5美元，但今天只卖4美元。
That's a sales promotion.
那也是销售促销。
Great.
很好。
So that's a really good marketing strategy.
这真是一个很好的营销策略。
Exactly.
没错。
So let's hear this word in our dialogue today.
那么我们来听听今天对话中的这个词。
Great.
很好。
So we are ready to listen to our dialogue.
现在我们准备听对话了。
It's going to be pretty fast.
语速会很快。
So it might be a little bit difficult to understand.
所以可能有点难懂。
But don't worry if you don't understand everything because later in this lesson we're going to
但如果你没全听懂也别担心，因为在本课后面我们会
explain all the important words and phrases.
解释所有重要的单词和短语。
All right, people, we're holding this meeting today because we've got to do something about
好了，各位，我们今天开这个会是因为我们必须想办法解决
our sales and we need to do it now.
销售问题，而且必须马上行动。
I want concrete solutions.
我要具体的解决方案。
How do you plan to drive sales?
你们打算如何推动销售？
Roger.
Roger。
Well, in fact, we're the most expensive in the market.
嗯，事实上，我们是市场上最贵的。
So maybe we need to lower our prices to match the competitors.
所以也许我们需要降价来匹配竞争对手。
Lower our prices.
降价。
Not very creative.
没什么创意。
It'll never fly with Swan.
斯旺绝对不会同意的。
What kind of thinking is that?
那是什么想法？
Geez.
天哪。
Anyone have a better plan?
谁有更好的计划？
Natalie.
娜塔莉。
Perhaps a promotion.
也许搞个促销活动。
Maybe a two for one offer or something like that.
比如买一送一之类的。
That's the same thing.
那还不是一样。
Bad idea.
馊主意。
Really bad idea.
非常馊的主意。
Damn it, people.
该死的，各位。
Come on.
拜托。
Think.
动动脑子。
We're going to be here any minute.
他随时都会到。
Hello, Mr. Swan.
您好，斯旺先生。
Oh, Mr. Swan.
哦，斯旺先生。
Hello, Mr. Swan.
您好，斯旺先生。
Do we have any ideas yet?
我们有什么想法了吗？
Yes, Mr. Swan.
是的，斯旺先生。
We were kind of considering a two for one offer to get more competitive.
我们刚才在考虑搞个买一送一的活动，提高竞争力。
A two for one promotion.
买一送一的促销。
Hmm.
嗯。
I kind of like the sound of that.
我有点喜欢这个主意。
It sounds like something we should consider.
听起来值得考虑。
Yeah, exactly.
对，没错。
That's just what I was thinking.
这正是我在想的。
In fact, it's a brilliant idea.
事实上，这是个绝妙的主意。
I'm glad we thought of that.
很高兴我们想到了这个。
Very creative.
非常有创意。
Okay, so an interesting manager, right?
好吧，一个有趣的经理，对吧？
I don't know about interesting.
我不觉得有趣。
Maybe I would think bad manager.
也许我会觉得是个差劲的经理。
We're going to talk about him later on in the show.
我们稍后会在节目中讨论他。
But now, let's take a look at our language takeaway.
但现在，我们来看看语言要点。
Language takeaway.
语言要点。
Okay, so language takeaway is the part of our lesson where we teach you the most important
好的，语言要点是我们课程的一部分，我们会教你们最重要的词汇。
words from the dialogue.
对话中的单词。
All these words that we are going to focus on can be found in today's dialogue.
我们今天要重点学习的这些单词都可以在今天的对话中找到。
Exactly.
没错。
So we have three words for you today.
今天我们为你准备了三个单词。
Let's look at the first one.
我们来看第一个。
Match the competitors.
匹配竞争对手。
Great.
很好。
So we have some examples for you so you can listen and try and see if you can figure out
所以我们为你准备了一些例子，你可以听一听，试着看看是否能理解
what match the competitors really means.
与竞争对手匹敌到底是什么意思。
Example one.
例子一。
We guarantee that we can match the competitors' lowest price.
我们保证能够匹配竞争对手的最低价格。
Example two.
例子二。
It's impossible for us to match the competitors.
我们不可能与竞争对手匹敌。
Our costs are just too high.
我们的成本太高了。
Example three.
例子三。
Do you think we can match our competitors' prices and still keep our quality high?
你觉得我们能在匹配竞争对手价格的同时保持高质量吗？
Ah, okay.
啊，好的。
So I see that match the competitors means to be as good as or better than other companies
所以我认为，match the competitors 的意思是与其他公司一样好或更好
in the same industry.
在同一行业中。
Exactly.
没错。
Match the competitors.
All right, so let's move to our second word today for Language Takeaways and it is in
好的，那么让我们进入今天语言要点的第二个词，它是
the market.
in the market.
In the market.
We heard this phrase in the dialogue and it means in the industry.
我们在对话中听到了这个短语，它的意思是在行业中。
Exactly.
没错。
I can say, for example, EnglishPod is the best language pod in the market.
比如，我可以说，EnglishPod 是市场上最好的语言播客。
So of all the podcasts that teach English, EnglishPod is the best.
所以在所有教英语的播客中，EnglishPod 是最好的。
Of course.
当然。
I'm not doubt about it.
我对此毫不怀疑。
I totally agree.
我完全同意。
Right.
对。
Or I can give you another example.
或者我可以再给你举个例子。
iPods are the most popular MP3 players in the market.
iPod 是市场上最流行的 MP3 播放器。
So of all the MP3 players in the world, iPods are the most popular.
所以在世界上所有的 MP3 播放器中，iPod 是最流行的。
So let's move to our final word for today and it is...
那么，我们进入今天的最后一个词，它是……
It'll never fly.
这绝对行不通。
It will never fly.
So this phrase sounds a little bit strange.
这个短语听起来有点奇怪。
I know.
我知道。
Fly?
飞？
Are we talking about an airplane here?
我们是在说飞机吗？
What's going on?
怎么回事？
Exactly.
没错。
But we're not.
但我们不是。
So we're going to give you some examples and try and guess what it'll never fly really
所以我们会给你一些例子，试着猜猜“it'll never fly”到底
means.
是什么意思。
Example one.
例子一。
This marketing plan will never fly.
这个营销计划绝对行不通。
It's just too expensive.
太贵了。
Example two.
例子二。
What you want to sell bikinis in Alaska?
你想在阿拉斯加卖比基尼？
That'll never fly.
那绝对行不通。
Example three.
例子三。
Brad told me his idea for a film script, but the story will never fly.
布拉德跟我讲了他的电影剧本创意，但这个故事绝对行不通。
It's not interesting enough.
不够有趣。
So it means it won't work.
所以它的意思是行不通。
It won't work.
行不通。
It's not a good idea.
不是个好主意。
They'll never agree.
他们绝不会同意。
Exactly.
没错。
Great.
太好了。
So now we've seen a lot of useful phrases and we are ready to listen to our dialogue
现在我们学了很多有用的短语，准备好听第二遍
a second time.
对话了。
But this time it's going to be slow.
但这次会慢速播放。
So you'll be able to understand a little bit better and you'll be able to hear the words
这样你就能更好地理解，也能听到我们刚刚讨论的
and phrases we were just talking about.
单词和短语。
All right, people.
好了，各位。
We're holding this meeting today because we've got to do something about our sales and we
我们今天开这个会是因为我们必须对销售采取行动，而且
need to do it now.
必须现在就做。
I want concrete solutions.
我要具体的解决方案。
How do you plan to drive sales, Roger?
你打算怎么提高销售额，罗杰？
Well, in fact, we're the most expensive in the market.
嗯，事实上，我们是市场上最贵的。
So maybe we need to lower our prices to match the competitors.
所以也许我们需要降低价格来与竞争对手匹敌。
Lower our prices.
降低价格。
Not very creative.
没什么创意。
It'll never fly with Swan.
斯旺绝不会同意的。
What kind of thinking is that?
那算什么想法？
Geez.
天哪。
Anybody else have a better plan?
还有谁有更好的计划吗？
Natalie?
娜塔莉？
Um, perhaps, um, a promotion, maybe a two for one offer or something like that.
嗯，也许，嗯，搞个促销，比如买一送一之类的。
What?
什么？
That's the same thing.
那不是一样吗。
Bad idea.
馊主意。
Really bad idea.
非常馊的主意。
Damn it, people.
该死的，各位。
Come on.
拜托。
Think.
动动脑子。
The CEO will be here any minute.
CEO随时会到。
Hello, Mr. Swan.
您好，斯旺先生。
Oh, Mr. Swan.
哦，斯旺先生。
Hello, Mr. Swan.
您好，斯旺先生。
Do we have any ideas yet?
我们有什么想法了吗？
Yes, Mr. Swan.
是的，斯旺先生。
We were kind of considering a two for one offer to get more competitive.
我们刚才在考虑搞个买一送一的活动，提高竞争力。
A two for one promotion.
买一送一的促销。
Hmm.
嗯。
I kind of like the sound of that.
我有点喜欢这个主意。
It sounds like something we should consider.
听起来值得考虑。
Yeah.
是啊。
Exactly.
没错。
That's just what I was thinking.
这正是我在想的。
In fact, that's a brilliant idea.
事实上，这是个绝妙的主意。
I'm glad we thought of that.
很高兴我们想到了这个。
Very creative.
非常有创意。
Okay, great.
好的，很好。
I hope everyone understands a lot better now.
希望大家现在都更明白了。
And I hope everyone could listen out for some of those key words.
希望大家能留意到那些关键词。
Right.
对。
So now it's time for us to take a look at Fluency Builder.
现在该来看看流利度构建器了。
Fluency Builder.
流利度构建器。
So with Fluency Builder, we try to help you increase your fluency.
通过流利度构建器，我们帮你提高流利度。
We take a word or phrase that you already know and show you how to say it a little bit
我们拿一个你已经知道的单词或短语，然后教你如何说得更自然一点，更像母语者。
more naturally, a little bit more like a native English speaker.
更自然一点，更像英语母语者。
Right.
没错。
And we have three of these words for you today.
今天我们为你准备了三个这样的词。
Yeah.
嗯。
Let's start with the first one.
我们先从第一个开始。
Okay.
好的。
So often students will say something like, I'll be here soon.
通常学生会说类似“我很快就到”这样的话。
Or I will arrive soon.
或者“我很快就到”。
Right.
对。
And these sentences are correct.
这些句子是正确的。
They're totally fine, but I think there's a better way to say this.
完全没问题，但我觉得有更好的表达方式。
Right.
对。
And we heard it in the dialogue, so let's listen to what the person in the dialogue
我们在对话中听到了，所以让我们听听对话中的人是怎么说的。
said.
说的。
The CEO will be here any minute.
CEO马上就到。
Okay.
好的。
So, be here any minute.
所以，“马上就到”。
He'll be here any minute.
他马上就到。
It just sounds a little bit more natural.
听起来更自然一些。
Yeah.
嗯。
I think I use this phrase quite often.
我觉得我经常用这个短语。
He'll be here any minute.
他马上就到。
He'll be here soon.
他很快就到。
Yeah.
嗯。
Great.
很好。
Okay.
好的。
So, let's move on to our second phrase for Fluency Builder.
那么，我们继续看流畅度提升的第二个短语。
So, this phrase will help you to learn how to say, I'm thinking about something in a
这个短语会帮你学会如何用更好听的方式表达“我在想某事”。
better sounding way.
更好听的方式。
Right.
对。
So, you can say something like, we are thinking about a sales strategy.
你可以说类似“我们在考虑一个销售策略”这样的话。
Or that sounds like something we should think about.
或者“这听起来像是我们应该考虑的事情”。
Right.
对。
And it's perfectly correct.
这完全正确。
Yeah.
嗯。
There's no problem with this.
这没问题。
But in the dialogue, we heard something a little bit different.
但在对话中，我们听到了一点不同的说法。
So, let's listen to it.
那么，我们来听一下。
It sounds like something we should consider.
听起来像是我们应该考虑的事情。
So, consider sounds like a pretty natural way of saying it.
所以，consider 听起来是一种很自然的说法。
Right.
对。
Yeah.
是的。
And you know, I think it sounds really kind of smart.
而且你知道吗，我觉得它听起来挺聪明的。
Yeah.
是的。
It sounds more formal even.
甚至听起来更正式。
A little more professional.
更专业一点。
Yeah.
是的。
It's a good word.
这是个好词。
Yeah.
是的。
Okay.
好的。
Brilliant.
太棒了。
So, let's move on to our third word.
那么，我们来看第三个词。
Marco, you already said our third word.
马可，你已经说了第三个词。
Oh, yeah.
哦，对。
I actually did.
我确实说了。
Brilliant.
太棒了。
That's a great word right there.
这个词很棒。
A lot of people might say, that's a great idea or great.
很多人可能会说，那是个好主意或者很棒。
But in the dialogue, we heard another way of saying the same idea.
但在对话中，我们听到了另一种表达同样意思的方式。
That's a brilliant idea.
那是个绝妙的主意。
Okay.
好的。
So, this is great.
所以，这很棒。
But I would have to say that it's a little bit more British English.
但我得说，这更偏向英式英语。
Yeah.
是的。
I'd agree with you there.
我同意你的看法。
But I also think it sort of gives more power to this idea that it's a good idea, brilliant
但我也觉得它给这个好主意增添了更多分量，brilliant idea。
idea.
主意。
And it's a really, really good idea.
而且这真的是一个非常非常好的主意。
Yeah.
是的。
I like that word.
我喜欢这个词。
Yeah.
是的。
Okay.
好的。
So, we're ready to listen to our dialogue again a third time, but at its normal speed.
那么，我们准备第三次听对话，这次是正常语速。
All right, people.
好了，各位。
We're holding this meeting today because we've got to do something about our sales and we
我们今天开这个会是因为必须得对我们的销售采取行动，而且
need to do it now.
必须立刻行动。
I want concrete solutions.
我要具体的解决方案。
How do you plan to drive sales?
你打算怎么提高销售额？
Roger.
罗杰。
Well, in fact, we're the most expensive in the market.
嗯，事实上，我们是市场上最贵的。
So maybe we need to lower our prices to match the competitors.
所以也许我们需要降价来和竞争对手持平。
Lower our prices.
降价。
Not very creative.
没什么创意。
It'll never fly with Swan.
斯旺绝对不会同意的。
What kind of thinking is that?
那算什么想法？
Geez.
天哪。
Anyone have a better plan?
谁有更好的计划？
Natalie.
娜塔莉。
Perhaps a promotion.
也许可以搞个促销活动。
Maybe a two for one offer or something like that.
比如买一送一之类的。
That's the same thing.
那还不是一样。
Bad idea.
馊主意。
Very bad idea.
非常馊的主意。
Damn it, people.
该死的，各位。
Come on.
拜托。
Think.
动动脑子。
The CEO will be here any minute.
CEO随时会到。
Hello, Mr. Swan.
您好，斯旺先生。
Oh, Mr. Swan.
哦，斯旺先生。
Hello, Mr. Swan.
您好，斯旺先生。
Do we have any ideas yet?
有想法了吗？
Yes, Mr. Swan.
是的，斯旺先生。
We were kind of considering a two for one offer to get more competitive.
我们正在考虑搞个买一送一的活动，来提高竞争力。
A two for one promotion.
买一送一的促销。
Hmm.
嗯。
I kind of like the sound of that.
我有点喜欢这个主意。
It sounds like something we should consider.
听起来值得考虑。
Yeah, exactly.
对，没错。
That's just what I was thinking.
这正是我在想的。
In fact, it's a brilliant idea.
事实上，这是个绝妙的主意。
I'm glad we thought of that.
很高兴我们想到了这个。
Very creative.
非常有创意。
I'm glad we thought of that.
很高兴我们想到了这个。
Very creative.
非常有创意。
I'm glad we thought of that.
我很高兴我们想到了这一点。
Very creative.
非常有创意。
I'm glad we thought of that.
我很高兴我们想到了这一点。
In fact, it's a brilliant idea I'm glad we thought of that.
事实上，这是个绝妙的主意，我很高兴我们想到了这一点。
Very creative.
非常有创意。
All right.
好吧。
So listening to this dialogue makes you think about this boss.
所以听这段对话会让你想到这个老板。
I'm pretty sure everyone has had a manager or a supervisor that's similar to this guy.
我敢肯定每个人都有过类似这样的经理或主管。
Yeah, this boss, Clark, I would have to say he sounds like a terrible person to work for.
是啊，这个老板，克拉克，我得说他听起来是个很糟糕的共事对象。
Yeah, that's true.
是的，没错。
If you're a manager, you want to motivate your employees.
如果你是经理，你想激励你的员工。
I think it's the most important thing a manager does is to encourage his or her employees
我认为经理最重要的事情就是鼓励他或她的员工。
and to help support them to grow and to be better people in the job.
并帮助他们成长，在工作中成为更好的人。
And this guy is totally not doing this.
而这个人完全没有做到这一点。
And you can tell because they are a little bit scared of talking and he cuts them off
你可以看出来，因为他们有点害怕说话，而他打断他们。
with saying, oh, it's a bad idea.
说，哦，这是个坏主意。
Give me a better idea and stuff like that.
给我一个更好的主意之类的话。
Yeah, I could never work for a guy like this.
是啊，我永远不可能为这样的人工作。
You know, my first boss that I had when I first entered the workforce, I was in a very
你知道，我刚开始工作时遇到的第一个老板，我当时职位很低。
junior position and I was working for a large company and the general manager of the company,
在一家大公司工作，公司的总经理。
he was amazing.
他非常棒。
He was so encouraging.
他非常鼓励人。
He knew every single employee's name, first name, and he would make an effort to stop
他知道每个员工的名字，是名字，而且他会特意停下来。
and say hello and ask them how things were going.
打招呼，问他们情况怎么样。
And you know what?
你知道吗？
This left me with such a good feeling about the company that I really wanted to work hard
这让我对公司感觉非常好，我真的想为公司努力工作。
for this company and try my best.
尽我最大的努力。
And I think that I've never met such a great boss as this guy.
我想我再也没遇到过像他这么好的老板了。
No, I think that's true.
不，我觉得确实如此。
Especially if you have a boss that's encouraging and motivating like that, it makes you work
特别是如果你有一个像那样鼓励和激励你的老板，会让你更努力工作。
harder and makes you feel part of a really special team.
让你觉得自己是一个特别团队的一员。
And that's something we can all agree on.
这是我们都能认同的一点。
And I'm sure all our managers out there do the same.
我相信我们所有的经理们也都是这样做的。
Well, you know what?
嗯，你知道吗？
I hope some of our listeners log on to our website and maybe they can tell us some experiences
我希望一些听众能登录我们的网站，也许他们可以告诉我们一些经历。
with bad managers or good managers or if they are managers, how they handle things.
关于糟糕的经理或好的经理，或者如果他们自己是经理，他们如何处理事情。
Yeah.
是的。
And hopefully they can use some of these great phrases that we talked about today.
希望他们能用到我们今天讨论的一些好短语。
Great.
太好了。
And be sure everyone to visit our website at EnglishPod.com and where you can find a
请大家务必访问我们的网站 EnglishPod.com，在那里你可以找到
lot of other information and really good resources to continue improving your English.
许多其他信息和非常好的资源来继续提高你的英语。
That's right.
没错。
So thanks for listening today everyone and until next time, this is goodbye.
感谢大家今天的收听，下次再见，拜拜。
Bye.
再见。